we are going into part one of the raw
some live show and that is the fitness
part I will do my workout and later
um record the food and the
Humanities parts
um
and you can now get these parts
separately I will also upload them
separately to my YouTube channel
so
in the food part I'll talk a little bit
more about how to make the wild pesto
and in the humanity part I will talk
about
money because it's such a big problem
for me right now that I
um yeah I want to talk about that and
what we may be able to do about it
for it
to get more of it
all of the above all right we are doing
the fitness part now
foreign
don't know what this story is with my
voice suddenly
cheers
okay I think one sweater can come off
oops
um okay
not do all the adjustments all right
there
that should work
okay
let's get this light in my face
yeah double sweaters yeah you know we
had it really hot at one point but no
we're back at 30s at night
and 50s in the day
so it's not exactly
summery weather
three days of 80s
got us all spoiled
okay
I'm all rusty
and the space is not like I like it but
that's what it is all right and reach
two three four five six seven eight and
swing
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
I love you my planet
I love you my sunshine
I love you Humanity definitely
I love you my body
all right
I have not had back issues even though I
have not done much twisting
but I think
my leg lifts and twisted leg lifts help
a lot too and I regularly do them at
night in bed
foreign
all right let's twist and one
two
four
five
six
seven eight and again
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight and one
bleed with your eyes
always have to remind myself as well
because when your thoughts wander your
eyes
Wonder two
but you're supposed to look as far as
you can it's an exercise for your eyes
too
three
four
five
six
seven
eight chicken and one
two
three
four
five
six
and one
two
three
four
five
six seven
[Music]
five six seven eight two more sets
three
four
six
seven eight last one
two Make It Count
four
five
six
seven
eight and slowly
knees hip waist chest shoulders neck
eyes
and this side and knees hip
my chest shoulders neck eyes
okay I'm getting hot
oh that was fast
and
the wave
okay
looking pink
down two three four and up six seven
eight and nine
three four and up six seven eight and
down
four and up six seven eight and down two
three four and up six seven eight down
and stay
and bounce two three four and five six
seven eight and bounce two three four
five six seven eight and bounce
don't put your arms out if it's too hard
six seven
to this side just a little tilt
four five
seven other side two
two four five six six seven eight and
Center two three four five six last one
and one two three
four
five
six
seven and curl up
reach two three four
six seven eight swing
two
three
four
we've had fires in the fireplace lately
so
there is
you know pieces of wood
flying around
okay I'm doing it first round of
weights
I made your two rounds not sure yet oops
that's excessive needles somewhere
no
we're ready back in front who won
two
three
four
five
six
seven eight again and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight to the side and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
to the ceiling
and
what
two
three
four
five
six
seven
elbows together and one
hey there long time no see
four three five
six
seven
eight
and
one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
that could have been better but
overhead to the back
and one
two
security
four
five
six
seven
eight oh
yeah
and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
[Music]
eight
diagonal
stand straight
and
one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
good
hey
baby hair flying into my mouth
ready
back in front and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight one more and one
two
[Music]
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
oh
yeah I definitely need to do another one
but maybe just with fivers
foreign
okay let's do some
squats
full squats you know the ones that I
have to
put my hands on the floor to get up
but that's something I really haven't
done so I need to
[Music]
have done this
have a little
glitter
but
oh this silliness of it all
all right and one
two
three
four and down
ah not bad tiny little push
not bad
okay let's do ten
and
my knees make these tiny little noises
like paper crunching or something
five
oh
I forgot to turn that off
okey-doke
and
one
two and down
somebody give me a hand
oh
you have no idea how happy I am that I'm
doing this
because I haven't done this workout in
Forever
and
I'm still trying
but it's future
I think we had 10 but I'm gonna try and
keep going for a bit
let's go to 20
yes we can
huh
you know
it's weird coming to terms with the fact
that
for the first time in my life I actually
have arm muscles in my 60s
but the skin keeps on
sagging wrinkling anyway so
I seem to have no influence over that
lately I've been dreaming of doing a
clay bath or something like that you
know the mud bath literally
I think I will
end
oh yeah
okay that was four more
six more to 20. we can do this
foreign
two more
and hmm
20.
his knees challenging me that's why I'm
gonna do two more
because
sorry darling you're not gonna get away
with
it
and
yeah
we totally can
all right Chair workout
on the edgy Edge Edge
and tilt
and kick your legs so one two three four
five this is pointed and then we flex
two three four five six seven two to the
right two three four five six uh this
side and point two three four five tails
seven and Center two three four five six
seven eight
[Music]
oh it's a little smelly here but
not really
oh
other side
and
a little water
this is spring water
it's just in a
bottle from
something else
that my son likes bubble
seltzer
oh
yes ma'am
okay we're going
on the other side both legs together
and
what one two three four five
six
seven eight and heels two
three
four five
six
seven two one
two
three four
five
six seven other side and one two three
four
five six seven Center and one two
three four relax that face six seven
eight
I'm gonna do a quick relax
chin forward
back straight As far as you can and then
collapse
and let it all dangle
now I have this
and curl up
and
we don't really need belly crunches
but
we'll do them anyway I mean actually
you know as we age we never get too much
abdominal workout it's just
oh
what is it with all this yawning
and tilt
I do my legs over cross you do you do
you
and now the important part is
to move your torso up and down
five
six
seven
eight chicken and one
two
three
four
five or two I needed after a seven eight
tilt one
two
four other side and one that's all I can
do
three
four
whoa
and here I'm thinking my leg lifts do
the trick
uh ah
yeah sitting here still right and
I'm supposed to be
doing the next move
and
that is a couple of plies
just two rounds of eight
ready go and one
two
just a little bit
four it's like the Demi PA the half plie
six
seven
eight
bounce your knees out your butt in
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah I have not done
these
it's what you get Johanna
oh
okay one more round
ready go
oh
but you
a three
the four
a five ah yeah yeah
and a dog
[Music]
oh Look whose voice is back
um
okay
that's it for cheerio
promised myself I'd do some
push-ups
I'd probably not from the floor
we're ready go and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
[Music]
celebrity flab
yes we can
yes we can yes we can can and no one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
yeah
can't get any lower than that sorry
you can do that
toes are cold
it's always a sign of exertion for me
he'd get cold toast
first
one more round ready go and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven eight
[Music]
foreign
that's not even too bad because it's
pretty Out Of Tune
but
okay one
small set of just two
things of butter sizes okay
on the floor
oh doggy style
okay
this the first one is in and out
and the second one is kicking to the
side okay
but of course we're doing both sides
first
I feel like starting with my left leg
for a change ready go and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven we go to twenty and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven eight four more and one
two
three
four
these leggings are too tight they hurt
in the knee pit
other side and who won
two
three
four
five
six
seven eight again and one
two
three
four
huh
six
seven eight four more and one
two
three
four
I feel like my face is hanging down to
the floor
mm-hmm
okay
to the side
and knee up doggy style and kick to the
side one
two
three
four
five
six
seven eight two again and one
two
three
four
five
six
seven eight four more
two three
I can feel that
I can feel
that I can feel that alone
other side
and who won two
three
four
five
six
seven
two
five
six seven eight four more and one two
three
four
hmm
foreign
okay
oh I said I would do another round of
weights I have to do that
oh
just the five Pounders mind you
put yourself in the face
ready go and one
two
three
five
six
seven
eight and one
two
three
four
five
six seven eight side one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
ceiling and
what
two
three
four
six
so
elbows and
one two
three
four
six
seven
eight and
now let's try get them really high one
two
three
four
five
six
seven eight
overhead to the back
for what
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
straight forward
who won
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
yeah you know
oh
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight and bouncing down
two
three
four
yeah
if I can friends and finish
oh
my scalp is sweating
like crazy and itchy
from the sweating and who won
two
three four
five
six
seven
eight last one
one two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight you
trying to see the temperature but
maybe it even made it to 60. wow
okay finishing up
reach two three four five six seven
eight
and swing
to
two three four
five
six
seven
eight
I love you my friend
planet
I love you my sunshine speaking still
doesn't work I love you Humanity
and I love you my body
all right
of course sometimes I'm tired
of this whole little planet thing
but then
all I need to do is a little workout and
bingo
I feel better I'm gonna let you out in a
minute darling
I'm just gonna finish this
[Music]
okay guys I'm gonna be right back with
the food recording but I'm going off
and coming back on
in a few
ciao